

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

INGO PYTHEAS FORRER NUILA

ABOUT ME:

Throughout my 5 years of experience as Graphic Designer, I have developed a keen eye for detail and a passion for creating designs that captivate and engage my clients, as a graphic designer with solid knowledge and experience in branding, corporate identity, content creation for social media, and marketing projects. Pleasant, cooperative, tactful and friendly, I am definitely ready to provide my services.

I take a holistic approach to design, incorporating both aesthetics and functionality into my work, my ability to understand and balance these elements has allowed me to create designs that not only look great, but also achieve their intended goals.

In addition to branding and corporate identity, I also have experience in content creation for social media and marketing projects. I understand how to create content that engages and connects with audiences, I have experience creating social media campaigns, email newsletters, brochures, and other marketing materials that help businesses achieve their marketing goals.

Overall, I am a highly motivated and detail-oriented designer with a passion for creating designs that not only look great but also serve a purpose.

EDUCATIONAL PATH:

2022

Training program Opportunity Web Development Zurich

2007 – 2010

Studied as a graphic designer / technician Universidad Technologica, El Salvador

1994 – 2006

Elementary school, high school and high school El Salvador

LANGUAGES:

German - B1 Level English - Advanced Spanish - Mother tongue

HOBBIES:

Participation in webinars with varied and high interest topics.

Attendance at various events associated with art and digital entertainment.

Tours with friends through the city and its various towns

Phone:
076 268 46 60
Email:
ingoproductions@gmail.com
Portfolio:
https://ingoforrer.netiify.app

TECHNICAL SKILLS:



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

2021 - 2022

Creation of physical and online magazines (Journal of Education and Entertainment) ChibiStories The Magazine, Zurich.

Responsible in the following areas:

- Conceptualization, and development of story, characters and content.
- Vectorization of elements as well as selecting high quality images and photos.
- · Creation of educational sections as well as entertainment within the magazine.
- In charge of the animation of the comic characters, to expand the concept to animated episodes.
- Creation of the website according to the high quality standards that characterize a UX/UI designer.
- Laying out the magazine for its subsequent printing and distribution.

Output:

- Build from scratch a physical and online magazine in a short period of time of two months and presenting a high
 quality product.
- Implementation of proper advertising campaign method accordingly with the magazine concept.
- Implemented with high quality a diverse web technologies for the expansion of the brand.
- Promoted superbly the comic through animated episodes, for further expansion of the product.

2020- 2021

German courses and work in the Gastronomy sector

2017 – 2019

Customer service and technical support staff SYKES El Salvador, PlayStation US&CA.

Responsible in the following areas:

- Determine problems related to the Internet connection, recognize the cause, and provide solutions
- Hardware repair in cases of users having difficulties at the moment of manipulating our products
- Carry out a careful analysis of any problem related to the Software and provide an intelligent and practical solutions.
- Help our users in cases of account recovery, always within a framework of total privacy, integrity, and professionalism.
- Making an exhaustive analysis within the framework of the company's policies in any users financial situation.
- Protect our community and report any case or situation in which our users have felt uncomfortable or harmed
- Help our users in the registration process concerning a shipment of one of our products for repair.

Output:

- Noteworthy solved different issues at once and give favorably resolutions attached to high business quality standards.
- Proficiently implemented the necessary soft skills for the correct understanding, analysis and subsequent solutions.

 Only the last of the correct understanding and subsequent solutions.
- Quickly build rapport with customers, combined with his technical knowledge meeting the company quality standards.
- Developed a splendid communication with clients, colleges and superiors due to an excellent command of 3 languages.
- Highly improved our customer satisfaction ratings by connecting professionally with our users.

2013 – 2015

Marketing & coordination for the project "Fan Club" (anime & comics, video games) Fan Fest Sv, El Salvador.

Responsible in the following areas:

- Structuring of various entertainment and exhibition areas
- Coordination of different contests as well as artistic exhibitions.
- Coordination of a team of at least 15 employees during the project.
- Creation and development of the brand, within graphic design.
- Creating and managing print and online ad campaigns as well as social media.
- Presentation of the project to subsequently obtain support from sponsors

Output:

- Remarkably managed large-scale projects regarding content, tasks and responsibilities.
- Coordinated an a marvelous way various shops and sponsors that participated in the festival.
- Directed and managed admirably a team thanks to a good handle of social and soft skills.
- Oversaw the logistics of the event, making sure that all the festivals is carried out properly.
 Promoted and fund raised fantastically the concept and idea of the festival obtaining a solid financed budget.

2011 - 2012 Various positions for various services in customer service and sales as well as financial issues.